injennieskitchen.com 2015-06-10

# Privacy Policy - In Jennie's Kitchen

By using, reading and accessing recipes from this site, InJenniesKitchen.com, you are accepting the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Why Are You Receiving Emails From Us?**

You may receive emails for the following reasons:

  * Your email address has been provided to us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future (“opt-in”) for our newsletter or when new content is posted;
  * You have purchased or registered or otherwise have an existing relationship with us.
  * You have left a comment, creating a conversation with the readers and owners of this website.

**Usage and Sharing**

We do not sell, share, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance written permission or unless ordered by a court of law.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website, which currently includes advertisements from Amazon ([http://www.amazon.com](http://www.amazon.com/)) and the Platefull network ([http://platefull.com](http://platefull.com/)), a subsidiary of General Mills. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). For example, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information, for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you. We may transfer the information that you have provided to us if InJenniesKitchen.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, InJenniesKitchen.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**How Can You Stop Receiving Email From In Jennie’s Kitchen?**

Each newsletter and subscription email has an unsubscribe link at the end of the email. Click on the link and follow the directions for removing your name from electronic delivery of updates and newsletters, for which you signed up for previously.

**Notice Regarding Online Behavioral Advertising**  
We allow third party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information  
when you visit our Web site.  These companies may use non-personally identifiable information  
(e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked  
or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide  
advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.  These  
companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.  To learn  
more about this behavioral advertising practice visit the NAI at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).  To  
opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

This policy is effective as of April 2012, and was last updated September 2013.
